Prophet T.B. Joshua, help me to walk properly!
Healing in Jesus' Name
Prophet T.B. Joshua was led by the unction of the Holy Spirit
to pray for the sick and afflicted, and miracles, signs and wonders followed.
Healing in Jesus' Name
Thank You, Jesus!
I came from Kang Won-Do and I am grateful! Hallelujah!
Healed in Jesus' Name
After a supernatural encounter with Jesus Christ in the power of the Holy Spirit,
Pastor Kim Hong Deok came back the next day of the South Korea Crusade
to testify to the world of his encounter with the Living God.
Let's hear from him.
SOUTH KOREA CRUSADE WITH T.B. JOSHUA
TESTIMONY TIME
South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Testimony Time
I am Pastor Kim Hong Deok,
I am from Kang Won-Do, South Korea.
South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Testimony Time
I came to receive healing for my fractured leg.
As a pastor, I climbed a ladder to repair a projector on the ceiling with one of the elders.
The ladder could not support the weight of two people and it broke.
I fell from three storeys high.
The doctors diagnosed that both my legs were fractured
and that my right leg was in a severe condition.
They had to place an artificial heel implant.
So, I was operated upon in a hospital.
South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Testimony Time
It has been six months since I did the operation.
The bones in my heel were shattered.
South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Testimony Time
The doctor had to put an artifical bone in my heel and used screws to fix it there.
Every time I walked, I suffered a lot of pain in my feet because of the screws.
When Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for me, the power of the Holy Spirit fell upon me.
After the prayer, I ran like this.
Hallelujah!
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Testimony Time
Thank You, Jesus!
Sir, we want you to explain what exactly happened to you yesterday
when Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for you. Just describe that experience.
I prayed
and when the power of God flowed through Prophet T.B. Joshua,
all the screws and iron in my feet melted.
I prayed for about a month before I came here and I was sure that God would heal my feet and heel.
God hears our prayers.
Believers all over the world who are watching this crusade, I believed God heard my prayer.
I knew I would share my testimony right here at the 2016 South Korea Crusade.
When Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for me, I felt the fire of the Holy Spirit working in my feet.
I instantly felt the fire of the Holy Spirit reach my foot as Prophet T.B. Joshua touched my body.
Thank You, Jesus Christ. We give all the glory to God Almighty.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time!
South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Testimony Time
Hallelujah! We know there are many people who are here waiting
to receive their own touch from Heaven today on the second day
of the 2016 South Korea Crusade with Prophet T.B. Joshua.
What is your advice to those who are present here and our viewers all over the world?
A prayer of faith will surely be fulfilled.
I pray that God will bless you all.
A prayer of faith will work and God will touch everyone in this room today.
God bless you. Thank you!
Amen. Thank You, Jesus Christ!
Finally, sir, for the glory of God, can you just one more time demonstrate
what you can do now that you could not do before.
I was limping like this before but I always testified that God would heal me.
God heard my prayer and I received my healing.
Hallelujah!
South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Testimony Time
Thank you!